rolereboot.org 2012-05-23

# Privacy

**Privacy Policy**

Role Reboot is committed to protecting your privacy. Role Reboot has created this Privacy Policy to explain why we collect particular information and how we will protect your personal privacy within our Web site. 

The following Privacy Policy governs the online information collection practices of www.rolereboot.com (the "Site"). This privacy policy does not apply to any information that you may provide to us or that we may collect offline or through other means (for example, via telephone or through the mail).

By visiting and using the Site, you agree that your use of our Site, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service. We may need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future; in that case we will post the changes to our Privacy Policy on the Site and update the effective date to reflect the date of the changes. If you use the Site after we post any changes, you accept the Privacy Policy as modified.

**How we collect and use information**

You do not have to identify yourself or provide your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address ("Personal Information") to use the Site.

If you should choose to give us your Personal Information, you decide how much information to provide. At various points we ask for your e-mail address, thoughts and comments. We will use your e-mail address to provide you news and information about Role Reboot.

Our general policy is not to make your Personal Information available to anyone other than our staff and agents. We may make Personal Information available to organizations with similar political objectives and viewpoints for the purpose of advancing our own political objectives. If you prefer we not share that information, please email **info [at] rolereboot [dot] org**.

We treat your first name, city, state, and any comments as Public Information. We may make your comments along with your first name, city, and state available to the public.

Non-identifiable website visitor data may be collected and used in aggregate to help shape, direct, and improve content of the Site.

We are required by state law to collect and report the name, address, occupation, and employer of individuals who make contributions to Role Reboot. This information is made publicly available by the government agencies with whom the committee files its reports.

**Cookies**

A "cookie" is a small data file that websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as user ID that the Site uses to math with the registration you already provided to us. The only information that a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. The Site uses cookies to authenticate the user and tailor your experience on the Site according to the preferences you specified.

Your browser is probably set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our Site will not function properly when you view them.

**IP Addresses and Log File Data**

The IP address is the location of your computer or network on the Internet. We log your IP address for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We also use page hits in the aggregate to track the popularity of pages that people visit in order to improve the quality of the Site. There is no Personal Information collected in our log files.

**Opting Out Information**

Subscribers to our email list may terminate their subscriptions via a link at the bottom of each email sent from [www.rolereboot.org](http://www.rolereboot.org/).

**Changes to Your Information**

You may change your subscriber information or change your information, at any time by contacting us at **info [at] rolereboot [dot] org**.

**Tell a Friend**

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our Site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. Role Reboot will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the Site. Role Reboot stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

**Children's Privacy Statement**

To help ensure the safety and privacy of children, we comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. We do not knowingly allow children under the age of 13 to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through the Site. The Site is not intended to solicit information of any kind from children under 13, and we have designed it to block our knowing acceptance of information from children under 13 whenever age-related information is requested.

If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of 13 as part of the Site, we will delete such information from our records.

**Security**

The Site has a number of security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control. Computer systems have restricted access limited only to those persons and organizations necessary to its proper functioning. This access applies to all electronic and physical security measures. Highly sensitive data including credit card information is additionally secured through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. Our servers are located in a locked, secure environment.

**Links**

The Site may provide links to a limited number of other websites whose privacy policies we do not control. Role Reboot, which pays for and authorizes this Site, is not responsible for the content or privacy policies of other websites. When you access another website through the links on this Site, the use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting, so please be sure to read the privacy statements for each website you visit.

**Questions**

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, the information we have collected from you online, the practices of this site or your interaction with this website, please contact us at **info [at] rolereboot [dot] org**.

Effective Date: December 2, 2010
